The animals filed slowly past, and each gazed his fill.
And Boxer put out his nose to sniff at the banknotes, and the flimsy white
things stirred and rustled in his breath.
Three days later, there was a terrible hullabaloo.
Whymper, his face deadly pale, came racing up the path on his bicycle, flung
it down in the yard, and rushed straight into the farmhouse.
The next moment, a choking roar of rage sounded from Napoleon's apartments.
The news of what had happened spread round the farm like wildfire.
The banknotes were forgeries. Frederick had got the timber for nothing.
Napoleon called the animals together immediately, and in a terrible voice
pronounced the death sentence upon Frederick.
"When captured," he said, "Frederick should be boiled alive."
At the same time, he warned them that after this treacherous deed, the worst was to be expected.
Frederick and his men might make their long-expected attack at any moment.